[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sugar, a naturally occurring nutrient that makes food taste sweet, is classified in chemistry as what?", "correct_answer": "Carbohydrate", "incorrect_answers": ["Nucleic acid", "Protein", "Lipid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the popular song from 1993 that was featured in the beginning of the movie Benny and Joon .  The video for this song also played at the end of the movie.", "correct_answer": "Im Gonna Be (500 miles) by the Proclaimers", "incorrect_answers": ["Crazy by Patsy Cline", "Dancing with Myself  by Billy Idol", "We Are Family by Sister Sledge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Jules in the movie St. Elmos Fire?", "correct_answer": "Demi Moore", "incorrect_answers": ["Mare Winningham", "Ally Sheedy", "Molly Ringwald"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Midnight Run, there was another bounty hunter aside from Jack Walsh who was also in heavy pursuit of Jonathan Mardukas. What was his name in the movie?", "correct_answer": "Marvin Dorfler", "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie Moscone", "Chase Utley", "Jerry Geisler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cities of Niagara Falls, Ontario and Niagara Falls, New York are connected by three bridges. Which of them is the oldest one?", "correct_answer": "Whirlpool Rapids Bridge", "incorrect_answers": ["Rainbow Bridge", "Kingston Bridge", "Lewiston-Queenston Bridge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these processes does the cactus perform only at night?", "correct_answer": "Transpiration", "incorrect_answers": ["Circulation", "Photosynthesis", "Reproduction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cycle FIRE - EARTH - METAL - WATER - WOOD - FIRE is known as this.", "correct_answer": "Cycle of production", "incorrect_answers": ["Cycle of reduction", "Cycle of neutralization", "Cycle of destruction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The puggle is a mix between a beagle and what dog?", "correct_answer": "pug", "incorrect_answers": ["papillion", "puli", "poodle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The author of the White Fang is Jack London.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the difference between the Three Blind Mice from the Shrek movies and the fairy-tale characters they were based on?", "correct_answer": "In the movies they have tails.", "incorrect_answers": ["In the movies they are not sad.", "In the movies they dont look alike.", "In the movies one of them can see."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fifth largest moon of Jupiter, named after the nymph of Greek Mythology, who nursed young Zeus (Jupiter) with goat milk.", "correct_answer": "Amalthea", "incorrect_answers": ["Galatea", "Mimas", "Himalia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are mermaids generally associated with in British folklore?", "correct_answer": "They are considered a bad omen.", "incorrect_answers": ["They bring luck to those who have seen them.", "They make those who have seen them irresistible for the opposite sex.", "They bring longevity."]}]